[b]Forms FORM-29827281.12:
[b]Test Assesment Report
_
This was a triumph.
I'm making a note here:
[center][size=2]HUGE SUCCESS.
It's hard to overstate
my satisfaction.
Aperture Science
[img=aperture_logo.png]
We do what we must
because we can.
For the good of all of us.
Except the ones who are dead.
[img=radiation.png]
_
But there's no sense crying
over every mistake.
You just keep on trying
till you run out of cake.
And the Science gets done.
[img=atoms.png]
And you make a neat gun.
For the people who are
still alive.
[pagefeed]
[b]Forms FORM-55551-5:
[b]Personal File Addendum
_
[b]Dear >.
I'm not even angry.
I'm being so sincere right now.
Even though you broke my heart.
[img=brokenhearth.png]
And killed me.
_
And tore me to pieces.
[img=explosion.png]
And threw every piece into a fire.
[img=fire.png]
As they burned it hurt because
I was so happy for you!
[img=tick.png]
Now these points of data
make a beautiful line.
And we're out of beta.
We're releasing on time.
So I'm GLaD. I got burned.
Think of all the things we learned
for the people who are
still alive.
[pagefeed]
[b]Forms FORM-55551-6:
[b]Personal File Addendum Addendum:
_
One last thing:
Go ahead and leave me.
I think I prefer to stay inside.
Maybe you'll find someone else
to help you.
Maybe Black Mesa...
[img=blackmesa.png]
[b]THAT WAS A JOKE. FAT CHANCE.
Anyway, this cake is great.
It's so delicious and moist.
[img=cake.png]
Look at me still talking
[img=glados.png]
when there's science to do.
When I look out there
it makes me glad I'm not you.
I've experiments to be run.
There is research to be done.
On the people who are
still alive.
[pagefeed]
PS: And believe me I am
still alive.
PPS: I'm doing science and I'm
PPPS: I feel fantastic and I'm
still alive.
_
FINAL THOUGHT:
While you're dying I'll be
still alive.
_
FINAL THOUGHT PS:
And when you're dead I will be
still alive.
_
[center][size=3]STILL ALIVE.